

CONTACT

- HossamHassanAli126@gmail.com
- 01061037112
- 1 Al Dear Bakri st., Moharram Bek
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/hossamin hassan-ali/
- 12/6/1997 司

SKILLS

- Digital campaigns
- Content Creation Copywriting
- Creative Writing
 Scriptwriting
- Making Content Strategies
- Making Digital Marketing Strategies
- Social Media Management
- Teamworking Leadership
- Time Management
- Self-confidence Problem solving
- Brainstorming Negotiation ●
- Creative think

HOSSAM HASSAN ALI

Content Creator & Creative Copywriter

I am a content Creator & Creative Copywriter Specialist in creating and writing creative content and producing valuable ideas for advertising and marketing. with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. I have a passion for digital marketing and advertising fields and I am trying to improve my personal skills to achieve my goals.

EDUCATION



Graduated from Faculty of English Commerce

Alexandria University (Class-2020)

WORK EXPERIENCE



Okyanos Business Development

May 2022 -Dec 2022

- Making Content Strategies for clients
- Making Content Plans Which includes (Text on Design Captions - Design visualization)
- · Making the ideas, scripts, and the voice over scripts of video ads.

Creators agency

Sep 2021 - May 2022 Freelancer

- Making Content Strategies for clients
- Making Content Plans Which includes (Text on Design Captions - Design visualization)
- · Making the ideas, scripts, and the voice over scripts of video ads.
- Create and manage advertising campaigns on , Facebook, Instagram

Icareer

Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

• Digital marketing intern

Kersh Keepers

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020 Moderator & Comic Maker

- respond to messages and comments including Facebook page & Group.
- Review and moderate all user-generated content and user profiles (either pre-, post-, or reactive moderation) within comments, images, videos.
- Create comics for all clients and publish them on the Kersh Keepers group to help the success of all campaigns and make it viral.

VOLUNTERING EXPERIENCE



- Social Media Member- AVAD Club (Alexandria Volunteers for Anti-Drugs)
- Social Media Member-SPARA (it is one of AVAD Club's projects, concerned about the environment, Consumption)
- Social Media Member "DAWSHA TE Team"

CERTIFICATIONS



- Digital Marketing Certificate from "GOOGLE"
- Content Creation Certificate from EAAC Group for Training & Consultancy
- Content Creation Certificate from Easy T.online
- Arab Academy for Science, Technology and Maritime Transport Diploma of Education, Digital Marketing

LANGUAGE

Arabic Native - English Very Good